ecomhunt.com 2019-12-11

# Ecomhunt - Privacy Policy Notice

Last Updated on Jan 25, 2018

**  
1\. Scope of this Privacy Policy; Information Collected**

Any Submission or other information you provide or is otherwise accessible to Ecomhunt (including from ancillary

services such as Facebook or Google+, as well as Apple or Android application markets, all owned and/or operated by

their respective owners, is considered, for the purpose of these Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy

hereunder, as Personally Identifiable Information.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any act or omission of any other person, third party entity or corporation, which

Ecomhunt does not own or control, or to individuals whom Ecomhunt does not employ or manage, including any of the

third parties to which Ecomhunt may disclose user information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

The contents of Submissions that have been delivered by the Ecomhunt Service or Application may not necessarily

copied, kept or archived by Ecomhunt in the normal course of business. You may not rely on Ecomhunt in any way with

respect to maintaining records of you activity.

 **2\. Use of Information by Ecomhunt**

Ecomhunt uses the Personally Identifiable Information you submit to us through the Application or Service, to operate,

maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service.

Ecomhunt may use non-personally- identifiable information (including user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser

type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Ecomhunt Application and Service.

 **3\. Collection of Information**

The Operator complies with web browser’s mechanisms to allow choice. When using the Application, you may choose

to stop sharing information at any time using your browser’s settings to disable the Application add-on. This will not

erase historic data. For erasure request please email: service@ecomhunt.com.

 **4\. Use of your Information**

Ecomhunt will not sell or share your Personally Identifiable Information (such as mobile phone number) with other third-

party without your consent or except as part of a specific offer or program or feature for which you will have the ability to

either opt-in or opt-out, and which may not financially charge you without your consent.

We may collect personally identifiable information about individual online activities over time and across different

websites using the Website, Application and Services.

 **5\. Data Security**

Ecomhunt uses reasonable commercially reasonable physical and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and

security of your personal information. Ecomhunt can not and does not ensure or warrant the security of any information

or Submission transmitted. Avoid unsecured or unprotected networks to submit messages through the Ecomhunt

Service.

 **6\. Children's Privacy**

If you are under 16 years of age, then please do not use the Ecomhunt Service or access the Ecomhunt Site at any

time or in any manner. If Ecomhunt learns that Personally Identifiable Information of persons under 16 years of age has

been collected using the Service, then Ecomhunt may deactivate the account and/or remove the Submissions or render

them inaccessible.

 **7\. Event of Merger, Sale, or Liquidation**

In the event that Operator is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right (or in the event of

liquidation, as provided under law) to transfer or assign the information collected from our users as part of such merger,

acquisition, sale, or other change of control.
